Guide to the Robert Flaherty Film Seminar Archive 1949 - 2011 MSS.326
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Flaherty Film Seminars
  - Subseries A: Audio Recordings
    - 11th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, 1965; ID: 326.0056 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0056, Box 74, Cd 326.0056)
      George Stevens, Jr, "Delta Phase One", Eskimo Artist:Kenojuac, "Death of the Hired Man", "New Shoes" Mr. Colon, Intro by G.S. to "Faces of America", "Architecture U.S.A", "Born a Man".
    - 11th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, 1965; ID: 326.0057 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0057, Box 74, Cd 326.0057)
      Duration: 54 minutes
      Original Number: 1965-13
      George Stevens discussions, Puerto Rican films, "La Esperanza" - comment, History of Flaherty seminar.
      Available
    - 11th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, 1965; ID: 326.0058 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0058)
      TRT: Unknown
      Original Number: 1965-14
      History of Seminar, Introduction to "Crazy Quilt", Discussion of "A Report" by Bruce Connor, Discussion of "The Inheritance" by Harold Mayer.
      Currently Unavailable.
    - 11th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, 1965; ID: 326.0059 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0059, Box 74, Cd 326.0059)
      Duration: 57 minutes
      Original Number: 1965-15
      Discussion of "The Inheritance" (continued), "A Regular Bouquet" (Mississippi), Comment "In the Street", "Entr'acte", "In a Dark Time".
    - 11th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, 1965; ID: 326.0060 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0060, Box 74, Cd 326.0060)
      Duration: 48 minutes
      Original Number: 1965-16
      Final Discussion.
    - 11th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, 1965; ID: 326.0061 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0061, Box 74, Cd 326.0061)
      Duration: 36 minutes
      Original Number: 1965-17
    - 12th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, 1966; ID: 326.0062 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0062, Box 74, Cd 326.0062)
      Duration: 47 minutes
      Original Number: 1966-01
      Discussion Rocha God/Devil.
    - 12th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, 1966; ID: 326.0063 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0063, Box 74, Cd 326.0063)
      Duration: 23 minutes
      Original Number: 1966-02
      discussion Sol Worth, Navajo, [TKI - Phila].
    - 12th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, 1966; ID: 326.0064 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0064, Box 74, Cd 326.0064)
      Original Number: 1966-03
      Discussion study film "L.A. Story"
    - 12th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, 1966; ID: 326.0065 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0065, Box 74, Cd 326.0065)
      Duration: 45 minutes
      Original Number: 1966-04
      discussion "Phyllis and Terry", [Storm] sequel, Jim Lipscomb.
    - 12th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, 1966; ID: 326.0066 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0066, Box 74, Cd 326.0066)
      Duration: 56 minutes
      Original Number: 1966-05
      "Bad Boys", [Bill Daniels], Ben Park, Intro to [Am. Film Trust].
    - 12th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, 1966; ID: 326.0067 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0067, Box 74, Cd 326.0067_pt.1, Cd 326.0067_pt.2)
      Duration: 87 minutes
      Original Number: 1966-06
      T. Hou, ["Children Adrift"], "Greek Heart".
    - 12th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, 1966; ID: 326.0068 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0068, Box 74, Cd 326.0068)
      Original Number: 1966-07
      N.E.T. - Curt Davis, Dr. Mason.
    - 12th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, 1966; ID: 326.0069 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0069, Box 74, Cd 326.0069)
      Original Number: 1966-08
      Harold Mayher, Dick [Keplan] E.R.S. Marv gold [Supprup].
    - 12th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, ID: 326.0070 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0070, Box 74, Cd 326.0070)
      Original Number: 1966-09
      Marv Gold - ["Superup"], "Loberstermen".
      Leonard Cohen, NATL Film Board and Canada, Tilton.
    - 12th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, 1966; ID: 326.0071 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0071, Box 74, Cd 326.0071)
      Original Number: 1966-10
      Tilton & AM. Film Institute, Mrs. Flaherty, Vertov- "Man with Camera".
    - 12th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, 1966; ID: 326.0072 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0072, Box 74, Cd 326.0072)
      Original Number: 1966-11
      Wednesday evening, Vertov - Man With Movie, Blind Child, Cacoot, Injured man, Cyclone, End of Trail, Phil Reisman
    - 12th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, 1966; ID: 326.0073 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0073, Box 74, Cd 326.0073)
      Original Number: 1966-12
      End of the Trail, Phil Reisman, AM Film Inst, AM Film Inst, Colin Young.
      Pauline Kael, [Peray Milir].
    - 13th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, September 3, 1967; ID: 326.0074 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0074, Box 74, Cd 326.0074)
      Original Number: 1967-01
      "The Riddle" - with Barbar Cornell, "Tiny Lund, Hard CHarger" with Charles Hartman and Lance Bird.
    - 13th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, September 3, 1967; ID: 326.0075 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0075, Box 74, Cd 326.0075)
      Original Number: 1967-02
      Children's Cultrual Foundation with Roger Larson, "Babbitt" with Arthur Barron and Barbara Connell.
    - 13th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, September 4, 1967; ID: 326.0076 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0076, Box 74, Cd 326.0076)
      Origianl Format: 1/4" audio reel
      Original Number: 1967-03
      "Araya" Margot Benacerraf, On Student Films.
    - 13th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, September 4, 1967; ID: 326.0077 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0077, Box 74, Cd 326.0077)
      Original Format: 1/4" audio reel.
      Original Number: 1967-04
      On Student Films.
    - 13th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, 1967; ID: 326.0078 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0078, Box 74, Cd 326.0078_pt.1, Cd 326.0078_pt.2)
      Duration: 104 minutes
      Original Number: 1967-05
      Discussion ending with Jack Willis- NET.
    - 13th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, 1967; ID: 326.0079 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0079, Box 74, Cd 326.0079)
      Original Number: 1967-06
      Bob [Machover], "Titicut Follies" Fredrick Wiseman.
    - 13th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, 1967; ID: 326.0080 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0080, Box 74, Cd 326.0080_pt.1, Cd 326.0080_pt.2)
      Original Number: 1967-07
      Beryl Fox, Farfield Peacock, Shirley Clarke Jason.
    - 13th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, 1967; ID: 326.0081 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0081, Box 74, Cd 326.0081)
      Original Number: 1967-08
      "Portrait of Jason" - Shirley Clarke, Part 2, "Warrendale" - Alan King, Part 1.
    - 13th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, 1967; ID: 326.0082 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0082, Box 75, Cd 326.0082_pt.1, Cd 326.0082_pt.2)
      Original Number: 1967-09
      Alan King - "Warrendale," Part 2, David Hoffman - ["Tin Page"], Harold Becker - "Sighet Sighet", Jack Robertson - ["The Way Rt ls"].
    - 13th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, ID: 326.0083 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0083, Box 75, Cd 326.0083_pt.1, Cd 326.0083_pt.2, Box 76, Dvd 326.0083_pt.3, Dvd 326.0083_pt.4)
      Duration: 176 minutes
      Original Number: 1967-10
      [Dom Prammybaker], Conclusion - Flaherty Institute.
      Access CD available. Please request parts 1, 2, 3 and 4
    - 14th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 23, 1968; ID: 326.0084 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0084, Box 75, Cd 326.0084_pt.1, Cd 326.0084_pt.2)
      Original Number: 1968-01
      W. Van Dyke, "Princess Newman" - Scott Bartlet, Mrs. Flaherty, Bob Nelson.
    - 14th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 24, 1968; ID: 326.0085 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0085, Box 75, Cd 326.0085)
      Original Number: 1968-02
      Frances Flaherty on the Louisian Study film, Lewis Freedman, Morton Silverstein.
    - 14th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, 1968; ID: 326.0086 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0086, Box 75, Cd 326.0086_pt.1, Cd 326.0086_pt.2)
      Duration: 78 minutes
      Original number: 1968-03
      Richard [Roud], Windhham, Godard, etc, introduced by Willard Van Dyke.
    - 14th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, 1968; ID: 326.0087 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0087)
      Original Number: 1968-04
      Discussion - Bruce Connor, "Cosmic Ray", "Report", "The White Rose".
    - 14th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, 1968; ID: 326.0088 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0088, Box 75, Cd 326.0088_pt.1, Cd 326.0088_pt.2)
      Original Number: 1968-05
      Jim McBride, David Holzman's diary, Black film Ben Land.
      Film on school, "Sometimes I even like me", Peter Levin, "The Queen" - Frank Simon.
    - 14th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, 1968; ID: 326.0089 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0089, Box 75, Cd 326.0089_pt.1, Cd 326.0089_pt.2)
      Duration: 81 minutes
      Original format: 1/4" audio reel
      Original number: 1968-06
      David Weiss, "No Vietnamese Ever called Me a Nigger".
    - 14th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, 1968; ID: 326.0090 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0090, Box 75, Cd 326.0090)
      Original Number: 1968-07
      "Still a Brother", Pan-African Arts Festival in Dakar.
    - 14th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, 1968; ID: 326.0091 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0091, Box 75, Cd 326.0091)
      Duration: 31 minutes
      Original Number: 1968-08
      Henry Brietrose introduced by Willard Van Dyke, discussing Propaganda as style and strategy and discussing film seen at Seminar.
    - 14th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, 1968; ID: 326.0092 (Box 2, Media ID: 326.0092, Box 75, Cd 326.0092_pt.1, Cd 326.0092_pt.2)
      95 minutes
      Original Number: 1968-09
      Jesse Owens Return to Berlin, Bod Greenspan.
    - 14th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, 1968; ID: 326.0093 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0093, Box 75, Cd 326.0093)
      Original Number: 1968-10
      Tim Asch, "Life in Orinoco".
    - 14th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, 1968; ID: 326.0094 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0094, Box 75, Cd 326.0094_pt.1, Cd 326.0094_pt.2)
      Duration: 84 minutes
      Original Number: 1968-11
      John Korty - "River Run"
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 27, 1969; ID: 326.0095 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0095, Box 75, Cd 326.0095)
      Original Number: 1969-01
      Discussion with Frances Flaherty
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 27, 1968; ID: 326.0096 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0096, Box 75, Cd 326.0096)
      Original Number: 1969-02
      Discussion with Jay Leyda
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 27, 1969; ID: 326.0097 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0097, Box 75, Cd 326.0097)
      Original Number: 1969-03
      John Whitney on Permutations, computer animation
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 28, 1969; ID: 326.0098 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0098, Box 75, Cd 326.0098)
      Duration: 26 minutes Original Format: 1/4" audio reel
      Original Number: 1969-04
      Perry Miller, Jack Venza, Vicki Hochberg, The Film Generation on Dance.
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 28, 1969; ID: 326.0099 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0099, Box 75, Cd 326.0099)
      Original Format: 1/4" audio
      Original Number: 1969-05
      Fred Wiesman
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 28, 1969; ID: 326.0100 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0100, Box 75, Cd 326.0100)
      Original Formta: 1/4" audio reel
      Original Number: 1969-06
      Stanton Kaye, "George & Brandy"
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 29, 1969; ID: 326.0101 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0101, Box 75, Cd 326.0101)
      Original Number: 1969-07
      Willard Vandyke: "Film is not a revolutionary instrument by itself."'
      Jack Willis on "Appalachio: Rich Land Poor People", Randy Abbotte- Harlem Workshop, [Tambellini]
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, August 29, 1969; ID: 326.0102 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0102, Box 75, Cd 326.0102)
      Duration: 28 minutes
      Original Number: 1969-08
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, August 29, 1969; ID: 326.0103 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0103, Box 75, Cd 326.0103)
      Original Number: 1969-09
      Donald Richie, Standing between two cultures, The irony of Cybele in a gilt frame, Dead Youth: pics. usually made for people, Difficult an dpersonal, How Fables made-orig. How feature originated, How dead youth orig.
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, August 30, 1969; ID: 326.0104 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0104, Box 75, Cd 326.0104)
      Original Number: 1969-10
      Dr. Ed Mason
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, 1969; ID: 326.0105 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0105, Box 75, Cd 326.0105)
      Original Number: 1969-11
      Boro Droscovic
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, 1969; ID: 326.0106 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0106, Box 75, Cd 326.0106)
      Duration: 4 minutes
      Original Number: 1969-12
      Draskovic
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, August 31, 1969; ID: 326.0107 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0107, Box 75, Cd 326.0107)
      Original Number: 1969-13
      Short films, Robin Crump, Peter Barton, Claudia, Will Hindle's "29: Merci Merci"
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, August 31, 1969; ID: 326.0108 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0108, Box 75, Cd 326.0108)
      Druation: 34 minutes
      Original Number: 1969-14
      Hans Richter
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, 1969; ID: 326.0109 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0109, Box 75, Cd 326.0109)
      Duration: 13 minutes
      Original Number: 1969-15
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, August 31, 1969; ID: 326.0110 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0110, Box 75, Cd 326.0110)
      Duration: 29 minutes
      Original Number: 1969-16
      Bob Breer
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, August 31, 1969; ID: 326.0111 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0111, Box 76, Cd 326.0111)
      Original Number: 1969-17
      Michael Snow
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, 1969; ID: 326.0112 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0112, Box 76, Cd 326.0112)
      Duration: 49 minutes
      Original Number: 1969-18
      Jay Leyda - "Earth"
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 19, September 1, 1969; ID: 326.0113 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0113, Box 76, Cd 326.0113)
      Original Number: 1969-19
      Arthur Barron
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 20, September 2, 1969; ID: 326.0114 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0114, Box 76, Cd 326.0114)
      Original Number: 1969-20
      Willard Van Dyke on film sponsorshipe ("Watersmith") -AFI - Will Hindle, Frances Flaherty on sponsorship, Arhtur Barron-Lee Myers, Willard- nature of the seminar, Phyllis Johnson, Jeff STrickler- must large meetings be emphasized, group size - formal paper- make a film- forum of Filmmakers- dope sheet- keep it informal
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 21, September 2, 1969; ID: 326.0115 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0115, Box 76, Cd 326.0115)
      Original Number: 1969-21
      Willard - criticism in disucssions "in a generous spirit", Time- too few films, too many, Robin Crump - "We are not all equal here." Everything is very unexpected - small groups more effective than large discussion.
      Boro Drascovicv - good to mix up the program. Arrange discussions chairs in circle - room for materials on filmmakers - Willard on "Easy Rider"
    - 15th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 22, 1969; ID: 326.0116 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0116, Box 76, Cd 326.0116)
      Duration: 10 minutes
      Original Number: 1969-22
      Frances Flaherty, Pudovkin, "The basic aim of cinema is to teach all people to see things new." "To see more is to become more. Deeper seeing is closer union. To see or to perish is man's condition, the condition thrust upon him."
    - 16th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, 1970; ID: 326.0117 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0117, Box 76, Cd 326.0117)
      Duration: 43 minutes
      Original Number: 1970-01
      Richter, Geo Amberg, Frances Flaherty
    - 16th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, duplicate, 1970; ID: 326.0118 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0118)
      Currently Unavailable
    - 16th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, 1970; ID: 326.0119 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0119, Box 76, Cd 326.0119_pt.1, Cd 326.0119_pt.2)
      Duration: 117 minutes
      Original Number: 1970-02
      Paul Ronder - "Second Chance", Hollis Frampton -
    - 16th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, 1970; ID: 326.0120 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0120, Box 76, Cd 326.0120_pt.1, Cd 326.0120_pt.2)
      Original Number: 1970-03
      Hollis Frampton, Cliff Frazier, Mark Sadan - "Indian Circle"
    - 16th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, duplicate, 1970; ID: 326.0121 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0121)
      Frampton, Cliff Frazier, Mark Sadan
    - 16th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, 1970; ID: 326.0122 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0122, Box 76, Cd 326.0122_pt.1, Cd 326.0122_pt.2)
      Original Number: 1970-04
      James Herbert, Morrissey, Jonas Meekas
    - 16th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, 1970; ID: 326.0123 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0123, Box 76, Cd 326.0123_pt.1, Cd 326.0123_pt.2)
      Duration: 116 minutes
      Original Number: 1970-05
      Jonas Meekas, Leonard Henny
    - 16th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, 1970; ID: 326.0124 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0124, Box 76, Cd 326.0124_pt.1, Cd 326.0124_pt.2)
      Duration: 126 minutes
      Original Number: 1970-06
      Kaylor interview, Bob Kramer - "Ice" and "People's War"
    - 16th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, duplicate, 1970; ID: 326.0125 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0125)
      Kaylor, Bob Kramer - "People's War" and "Ice"
    - 16th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 27, 1970; ID: 326.0126 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0126, Box 76, Cd 326.0126_pt.1, Cd 326.0126_pt.2)
      Original Number: 1970-07
      Interview with Sumner Glimcher, Erik Barnouw, Paul ronder, Barbara Van Dyke re: "Hiroshima/Nagasaki", Interview with Robert PBB Hughes re: "Arthur Penn"
    - 16th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, duplicate, 1970; ID: 326.0127 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0127)
      Barnouw, Ronder, Glimcher, B. Van Dyke- "Hiroshima", Robert Hughes - -"Arthur Penn"
    - 16th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, August 28, 1970; ID: 326.0128 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0128, Box 76, Cd 326.0128_pt.1, Cd 326.0128_pt.2)
      Duration: 128 minutes
      Original Number: 1970-08
      Madeleine Anderson: "I'm Somebody", Standish Lauder: disucssion of his 4 films, [Bertucelli]: "Walls of Clay"
    - 16th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, August 28, 1970; ID: 326.0129 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0129, Box 76, Cd 326.0129_pt.1, Cd 326.0129_pt.2)
      Duration: 122 minutes
      Original Number: 1970-09
      Sol Landau on "Fidel", William Boyer, "Mississippi Summer"
    - 16th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, 1970; ID: 326.0130 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0130, Box 76, Cd 326.0130_pt.1, Cd 326.0130_pt.2)
      Duration: 108 minutes
      Original Number: 1970-10
      William Beyer on "Mississippi Summer", Ken Jacobson "Tom, Tom, the Piper's Son"
    - 16th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, duplicate, 1970; ID: 326.0131 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0131)
      William Beyer, "Mississippi Summer", Ken Jacobson, "tom, Tom, the Piper's Son"
    - 16th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, 1970; ID: 326.0132 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0132, Box 76, Cd 326.0132_pt.1, Cd 326.0132_pt.2)
      Duration: 130 minutes
      Original Number: 1970-11
      Hilary Harris on "The Nuer", Final Rap Session
    - 16th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, duplicate, 1970; ID: 326.0133 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0133)
    - 16th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, August 30, 1970; ID: 326.0134 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0134, Box 76, Cd 326.0134)
      Duration: 71 minutes
      Original Number: 1970-12
    - 16th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, duplicate, 1970; ID: 326.0135 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0135)
      Final session
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, 1971; ID: 326.0136 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0136, Box 76, Cd 326.0136)
      Original Number: 1971-01
      Dusan Makavejev - "Love Affair", Robert Kaylor - "Derby"
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, 1971; ID: 326.0137 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0137, Box 76, Cd 326.0137)
      Duration 66 minutes
      Original Number: 1971-02
      Dusan Makavejev - "Love Affair", "Roller Derby"
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 22, 1971; ID: 326.0138 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0138, Box 76, Cd 326.0138)
      Original Number: 1971-03
      Rolly, "Sad Song of Yellow Skin", Dr. Mason
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 22, 1971; ID: 326.0139 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0139, Box 76, Cd 326.0139)
      Original Number: 1971-04
      Continuation of "Yellow Skin", Willard V. Dyke - documenting the 1930s
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, 1971; ID: 326.0140 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0140, Box 76, Cd 326.0140)
      Original Number: 1971-05
      Dr. Edward Mason "Let There Be Light", David Sheppard talking on "Directed" by John Ford
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, 1971; ID: 326.0141 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0141, Box 76, Cd 326.0141)
      Original Number: 1971-06
      De Antonia & "Mill House"
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, 1971; ID: 326.0142 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0142, Box 76, Cd 326.0142)
      Duration: 63 minuted
      Original Number: 1971-07
      [Don Lenzer]
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, 1971; ID: 326.0143 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0143, Box 76, Cd 326.0143)
      Original number: 1971-08
      Don Lenzer - "A Wonderful Construction", Jay Ruby - "Imaginero", William Greaves - "The Voice of La Raza" (1972)
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, 1971; ID: 326.0144 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0144, Box 76, Cd 326.0144)
      Original Number: 1971-09
      Imaginero: discussion led by Jay Ruby, Discussion with Bill Greaves, "The Muder of Fred Hampton" with Mike Gray
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, 1971; ID: 326.0145 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0145, Box 76, Cd 326.0145)
      Original Number: 1971-10
      Mike Gray - "Fred Hampton", Julia Reichert and Jim Klein on "Six Into One" (#1)
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, 1971; ID: 326.0146 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0146, Box Shared Fales 134, Cd 326.0146)
      Original Number: 1971-11
      Mike Gray - "Murder of Fred Hampton", As Six Become One, Julia Reichert and Jim Klein
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, 1971; ID: 326.0147 (Box 3, Media ID: 326.0147, Box Shared Fales 134, Cd 326.0147)
      Original Number: 1971-12
      Reichert and Klein - "Six Into One", Nick Doob - "Set-Up"
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, 1971; ID: 326.0148 (Box 4, Media ID: 326.0148)
      Original Number: 1971-13
      Nick Doob Makaveyev - "Innocence Unprotected"
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, 1971; ID: 326.0149 (Box 4, Media ID: 326.0149)
      Original Number: 1971-14
      Makavejev - "Innocence Unprotected" Brayton Harris - "Selling of the Pentagon" Amalie Rothschild - "The Center" Peter Werner - "Hidden & Seeking"
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, 1971; ID: 326.0150 (Box 4, Media ID: 326.0150)
      Original Number: 1971-15
      continuation of Brayton Harris - "Selling of the Pentagon" beginning of Amalie Rothschilde - "The Center" Hoa Binh
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, 1971; ID: 326.0151 (Box 4, Media ID: 326.0151)
      Original Number: 1971-16
      Peter Werner - "Hidden & Seeking" Makavejev on "W.R." Begin Walter Ungerer - "Keeping Things Whole"
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, 1971; ID: 326.0152 (Box 4, Media ID: 326.0152)
      Original Number: 1971-17
      Makavejev - "W.R. Mysteries of the Organism"
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, August 24, 1971; ID: 326.0153 (Box 4, Media ID: 326.0153)
      Original Number: 1971-18
      Makavejev - "W.R. Mysterious of the Organism" Jack [Ofield], Arthur [Littman] - "Different Sans"
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 19, 1971; ID: 326.0154 (Box 4, Media ID: 326.0154)
      Original Number: 1971-19
      Walter Ungerer - "Keeping Things Whole" Oldfield and Littman - "Different Sons"
      Barbara Loder - "Wanda"
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 20, 1971; ID: 326.0155 (Box 4, Media ID: 326.0155)
      Original Number: 1971-20
      Barbara Loden - "Wanda" James Card
    - 17th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 21, 1971; ID: 326.0156 (Box 4, Media ID: 326.0156)
      Original Number: 1971-21